{
  "quiz2": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "questionType": "multiple_choice",
      "questionText": "1. How do you insert comments in Java code?",
      "correctAnswer": "//comment",
      "options": ["//comment", "#comment", "/*comment", "/comment/"],
      "feedback": ["Correct!"]
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "questionType": "multiple_choice",
      "questionText": "2. Which is a Java Operator",
      "correctAnswer": ["All of the above"],
      "options": ["+ sign", "* sign", "- sign", "All of the above"],
      "feedback": ["Correct!"]
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "questionType": "true_false",
      "questionText": "3. Java is short for JavaScript.",
      "correctAnswer": "False",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "feedback": ["Correct!"]
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "questionType": "multiple_choice",
      "questionText": "4. Which data type is used to create a variable that should store text?",
      "correctAnswer": "String",
      "options": ["String", "string", "Txt","myString"],
      "feedback": ["Correct!"]
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "questionType": "text_input",
      "questionText": "5. The ___ operator is used to add together two values",
      "correctAnswer": "+",
      "answerFieldId": "answer_to_question",
      "feedback": ["Correct!"]
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "questionType": "multiple_choice",
      "questionText": "6. How do you create a variable with the numeric value 5?",
      "correctAnswer": "int x=5;",
      "options": ["int x=5;", "num x=5", "x=5;", "float x=5;"],
      "feedback": ["Correct!"]
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "questionType": "text_input",
      "questionText": "7. The ___ operator is used to multiply together two values",
      "correctAnswer": "*",
      "answerFieldId": "answer_to_question",
      "feedback": ["Correct!"]
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "questionType": "multiple_choice",
      "questionText": "8. Which method can be used to find the length of a string?",
      "correctAnswer": "length()",
      "options": ["length()", "len()", "getLength()", "getSize()"],
      "feedback": ["Correct!"]
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "questionType": "multiple_choice",
      "questionText": "9. Which method can be used to return a string in upper case letters?",
      "correctAnswer": "toUppercase()",
      "options": ["toUppercase()", "touppercase()", "tuc()", "upperCase()"],
      "feedback": ["Correct!"]
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "questionType": "text_input",
      "questionText": "10. Declare a Java String variable named firstName",
      "correctAnswer": "String firstName;",
      "answerFieldId": "answer_to_question",
      "feedback": ["Correct!"]
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "questionType": "multiple_choice",
      "questionText": "11. To declare an array in Java, define the variable type with:",
      "correctAnswer": "[]",
      "options": ["[]", "()", "{}", "\/"],
      "feedback": ["Correct!"]
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "questionType": "multiple_choice",
      "questionText": "12. How do you create a method in Java?",
      "correctAnswer": "methodName()",
      "options": ["methodName.", "(methodname)", "methodName()","methodName[]"],
      "feedback": ["Correct!"]
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "questionType": "multiple_choice",
      "questionText": "13. How do you call a method in Java?",
      "correctAnswer": "methodName();",
      "options": ["methodName();", "methodName;", "methodName[];", "(methodName);"],
      "feedback": ["Correct!"]
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "questionType": "multiple_choice",
      "questionText": "14. Which keyword is used to import a package from the Java API library?",
      "correctAnswer": "import",
      "options": ["getlib", "import", "package", "lib"],
      "feedback": ["Correct!"]
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "questionType": "text_input",
      "questionText": "15. Array indexes start with:",
      "correctAnswer": "0",
      "answerFieldId": "answer_to_question",
      "feedback": ["Correct!"]
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "questionType": "multiple_choice",
      "questionText": "16. Which keyword is used to return a value inside a method?",
      "correctAnswer": "return",
      "options": ["get", "break", "return", "void"],
      "feedback": ["Correct!"]
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "questionType": "true_false",
      "questionText": "17. Break is a statement that is used to stop a loop",
      "correctAnswer": "True",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "feedback": ["Correct!"]
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "questionType": "true_false",
      "questionText": "18. Java is case-sensitive",
      "correctAnswer": "True",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "feedback": ["Correct!"]
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "questionType": "true_false",
      "questionText": "19. In Java, it is possible to inherit attributes and methods from one class to another.",
      "correctAnswer": "True",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "feedback": ["Correct!"]
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "questionType": "true_false",
      "questionText": "20. Package is the keyword used to import a package from the Java API library",
      "correctAnswer": "False",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "feedback": ["Correct!"]
    }
  ]
}
